

+234 704 182 0396

martinohez@gmail.com



Full-Stack Developer

44, Sunday bada street, Ojo, Lagos 🕡



# Side projects

- Burger Site
- martins-burger.vercel.app
- My portfolio
- martinsohezportfolio.vercel.app
- Meals app
- martinsmealsapp.vercel.app

## Skills

- · Problem solving
- · Proficiency in troubleshooting software issues and debugging a large codebase
- Communication skills
- Able to work collaboratively
- · Software programming languages
- · Graphic Design
- Video Editing

### **ADDRESS**

44, Sunday Badia Street, Ojo, Lagos

### **EMAIL**

martinohez@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/martins-ohez-7bb7731a2

### **GitHub**

https://github.com/Martin-IJ

### Phone:

+234 812 570 6803

# **Profile**

A qualified software engineer with over 2 years experience with an excellence skill in analyzing and modifying existing software, as well as developing, and testing end-user applications that match user needs all using software programming languages like JavaScript, React, Python and Django and frameworks like Bootstrap and Tailwind.

# **Work Experience**

Tech Studio | March 2023 - June 2023

## **Software Engineer Intern**

Internship

Florintech Computer College | April 2022

### **Junior Software Engineer**

• Front-end web development (Tutor)

Kingdom Power Int'l | 2018 - 2023

### **Technical Director**

· Provides technical support, project manager and social media manager

# **Education**

University of Lagos | 2022 - Date

Senior Secondary School Certificate (SSCE)

LightBearers College | 2013 - 2018

Senior Secondary School Certificate (SSCE)

Crowned Success Int'l School | 2004 - 2012

First School Leaving Certificate (FSLC)